今晚就走
we leave tonight
没有电
It's got no electricity
也没自来水
And no running water.
一百块一个月
A hundred bucks a month.
可以
Deal.
准备好了?
Ready?
希望这能行的通 兄弟
I hope this works, popi.
你的那本书 上面都是些坐标
That book of yours it's just a bunch of coordinates
是吧?
In there, right?
还有些其他的
Among other things.
你爸爸是否还记得
Does your father still have
我上次给你的电话号码?
That phone number I gave you?
我想是的
I think so.
好 让他打电话给我哥哥
Well, tell him to call my brother.
爸爸 帮我朋友打那个电话
Papa, make that call for my friend.
那美国人?
The american?
如果时间到了
If time runs out,
我还没有拿到另一半坐标
And I don't have the second half of those coordinates,
Lj 和 这位小姐就会没命
Lj and the senorita stop breathing.
外面有你的悬赏通缉令
you have a warrant out for your arrest
你哪儿都不能去
you are not going anywhere
但愿还有别的办法
Just wish there was another way to do is.
能够救出lj 同时不把惠斯勒交给他们
To save lj without handing Whistler over.
听着 只能这样了 没别的办法
Look, man, that's it there isn't.
那是什么?
What is that?
凯斯力氟(一种化学剂)
Kesslivol.
当加热到一定程度
When heated to a certain degree,
就能腐蚀金属
It eats through steel.
一旦林肯切断电源 我们就马上行动
As soon as linc cuts the power we go.
那后备电源呢?
What about the backup generator?
在断电的刹那与后备电源启动间
There's a lag from when the power cuts out
有个时间差
To when the generator kicks back in.
多长时间?
How long a lag we talking about?
30 秒
30 seconds.
只有30秒 快
We only have 30 seconds. go.
快点 快点
Move it, move it.
全都黑乎乎的
everything's dark
来啊
Come on.
走
Let's go.
-好了 快走 -还不行
Okay, let's go. not yet.
得走了 没时间了
We have to go now. we're running out of time.
相信我
Trust me.
停下 否则我们开枪了
stop, or we'll shoot
停下
stop
快啊 伙计
Come on, mate.
迈克 为什么停下?
What's the holdup, Michael?
再等等
Just a little bit longer.
停下
stop
怎么了?
What happened?
他们被逮到了
They got caught.
-怎么回事? -闭嘴
What's going on? shut up.laring)
怎么 怎么 ?
What, what ?
老实点
Don't try anything.
把他们带过来 把他们带过来
Bring 'em over here bring 'em over here
你 跪下
You on your knees, get down
别动
Don't move,
动一动就让你像他那样
Or you're like your friend over here.
迈克 到底怎么了?
What's going on, Michael?
这里发生越狱事件
we have an escape in progress
发生越狱事件
we have an escape
这次最好能成功
This sure as hell better work out.
对大家都好
For everyone's sake.
什么情况?
staus?
没有发现其他犯人
no other prisoners have been found
你们俩
You two,
站起来
On your feet.
带他们进去
bring them inside
走
move
-斯科菲尔德 在哪? -闭嘴
Where the hell's Scofield? shut it.
如果斯科菲尔德 没被逮到
If Scofield doesn't get caught,
他就还会有办法的
He could still fix this mess.
把这流血的杂种
have someone drag in
给我拖进去
the bleeding pig
快点
hurry it up
我们现在怎么办?
What do we do now?
灯还亮着 他们都知道了
The lights are on, they know about the escape what's your plan,
你到底有何计划 迈克?
Michael?
这就是计划
This is the plan.
YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
最新最快字幕下载请登录：www.YYeTs.net
■
字幕：YYeTs人人影视字幕组  后期：梁良
迈克 怎么
Michael, how the hell
难道他们被逮住也是你的计划?
Is getting caught your plan?
你告诉他们有30秒时间可以穿越的
You told them they had 30 seconds to get across
但事实上 你知道没那么久
When you knew the generator was going to kick in sooner.
我一定是算错了
I must have miscalculated.
再过10分钟 太阳就要升起了
We've got about ten minutes till the sun rises.
还有巡逻的警卫呢
And there are soldiers out there, okay.
他们会点人数的 我们得回去
They'll take count. we got to get back to the yard.
我们就待在这儿
We're not going anywhere.
时间就快到了
It's almostime.
-你在干吗? -可能是我太太
What do you tnothing. it's just probably my wife.
你知道 我们就住在不远处
You know, we live a couple miles away
她可能听到了警报声 所以就
And she must have heard the sirens, so
等我处理完你 你再打电话
You can make your calls when I'm done with you.
你还带了什么?
What else you got?
-苏克雷? -我不在 有事留言
Sucre? I'm not here. say what you got to say.
苏克雷 你到底在哪?
Sucre, where the hell are you?
我们现在全靠你了
We're counting on you to be here
没有你 我们就全完了 老兄
If you're not there, we're dead, man.
快回我电话
Now call me back, please.
把这些和他的私人物品放一起
Put these with his personal effects.
到底出什么事了?
What's going on out there?
有犯人想越狱
Some prisoners tried to escape.
逃出去了么?
Did they get out?
被抓到了
They got caught.
有一个还伤的挺严重
One of them got shot pretty bad.
苏克雷?
Sucre?
不 我是 阿方索·加利西亚
No, it is Alphonso Gallego.
你到了那儿?
You where you need to be?
是的
Yes.
我把车子停在了马路边上
I left the suburban on the side of the road.
钥匙在轮胎上
The keys are in the wheel well.
去看看在不在
Are they still t hecheck 'em out.
在的
They're here.
好 好的
Good, good.
你也来这儿么?
You will be here too,
312 ?
On the 312?
是的 是的 312
Yeah, yeah, the 312.
到时见
See you there.
所有人都在这了?
These all the men? si, senor.
老实交待你们是怎么到那的?
Tell me, how did you get out there?
你们是怎么到那的?
How did you get out there?
有人想说吗?
Hmm? don't want to tell me?
你们是怎么到那的?
How did you get out there?
有个通道
A tunnel.
在哪?
Where?
在勒齐的房间下面
Under Lechero's room.
带路
Show me.
还要多久?
How much longer?
没几秒了
It's just a matter of seconds now.
迈克?
Michael?
开门
The door.
我不知道密码
I don't know the combination.
那就砸了它
Then improvise.
真是太疯狂了
This is insane.
走了
Let's go.
进去
Vamanos.
加紧
Hurry
没东西
nothing
你确定?
you're sure?
确定
absolutely
该死的 让他们给逃了
it's son of bitch so is out
你确定?
are you certain?
确定
absolutely
是空的
it's empty
不是我
It wasn't me
是斯科菲尔德 是他做的
It was Scofield he did this
只要检查院子 他和
Just check the yard him,
惠斯勒 马宏和那个篮球小子
Whistler, Mahone and that basketball kid
他们到不了那里的
None of 'em will be there
点完人数了么?
did you finish the count?
快点完了 长官
just finishing now, sir
长官 少了四个
sir we are four short
这里是solo长官 其他的犯人不见了
This is captain solo. other inmates are missing.
给我全面封锁这里
I want a post-and-protect
以及监狱周边地区
Around the entire perimeter of the prison.
将军 没找到有人
General, we see no one.
你确定有犯人逃出去了?
Are you sure there's prisoners out here?
没他们的地方 你当然找不到他们
You won't find the prisoners here in no-man's-land
因为他们已经走了
Because they're already gone.
快点 我们要跟丢了
faster. we're losing them
他一上来就大声的喊
he just started shouting
要我们下车
to get off the bus
快下车
Off the bus now
Get off the
快走
Bunow
能描述下疑犯么?
how would you describe the suspect?
可以 他高高的个子
well, he was tall
有6尺多高
more than six feet
哪国人?
what nationality?
美国人
american
他说英语的
he spoke English
再见到他 你能认出来么?
if you saw him, would you recognize him?
是的 当然了
yes, of course
怎么了
What's wrong?
我扭到脚了 脱臼了
My ankle I've torn it apart
快跟上
Come on.
没那么远了 加把劲
It's not that far. help me up
惠斯勒先生 那就拽你头发 拖你走
Mr. Whistler, we'll drag you by your hair
因为我们必须走
Because we got to go
我会连累你们的 快走吧 别管我
I'll slow you down. just go just leave me
我们都知道这行不通
We both know that's not an option.
离海岸很近了
It's only a quarter
只有四分之一英里了
Of a mile to the beach.
只要我们坚持 一定能到那的
If we stick to the bush, we can make it.
阿历克斯 来帮下忙
Alex, a little help?
走 快点
Go. come on
我们只有几分钟时间
Hey. we only have a few minutes.
后面有士兵追着
We got soldiers right behind us.
还有警察
Cops as well.
得到我们要的了吗
We got what we nd?
恩 得到了
Yeah, we got what we need.
我们需要什么
What do we need?
总是会遇到这样的情况
Always picking up the strays, huh?
这边走
This way.
快 走吧
come on. let's go
听着 迈克 如果你以为把我交给他们
Listen, Michael, if you think the company's just going
他们就会放了你侄子 那你就错了
To let you swap me for your nephew, you're mistaken.
闭嘴
Shut up.
一旦他们得到了我
Once they get hold of me,
他们就会杀了你们所有人
They're gonna kill all of you,
而我也不想索菲亚在混乱中被抓
And I don't want Sofia caught in the crossfire.
让我走吧
Listen, just let me go.
我会联系他们的 我发誓
I'll contact them, I promise.
一旦知道LJ安全了 我就会去自首
I'll say I'll turn myself in once I know lj's safe.
听好了 不许你提我儿子一个字
Hey, you got no say in wha happens to my son you got it?
我们不是来这享受日光浴的
We don't need a suntan.
我们得赶紧消失
We need to get lost.
监狱沿线都有军队守卫在巡逻着
The military patrols all the roads around the prison.
你不考虑乘船?
You didn't consider a boat?
他们一出现 我们只离岸10码
They show up here and we're ten yards off the shore,
不是都成了活靶子
We're target practice.
我们得赶紧消失
We need to be invisible.
5人只有4氧气罐
Five guys, four tanks.
去死吧 马宏
Sucks for you, Mahone.
我和林肯分享
Lincoln and I will share.
把鞋子扔在盒子里
Toss your boots in the box.
喂
Yeah?
告诉我 你已经带他出来了
Tell me you have him.
是的 在我手上
Yeah, I got him.
我儿子在哪里?
Where's my son?
在我边上 马上让他听电话
With me. put him on the phone now.
说话吧
Say something.
我很快就过去 别伤了任何人
I'll be there soon. just don't hurt anyone.
你满意了吧?
You happy?
20分钟后 巴拿马城
You have 20 minutes to meet me in panama city
我们说定的地方见
Where we agreed.
我们会去的
We'll be there.
我得把书放进去
Hey, I need to put my book in there.
书呢? 我的书呢?
The book? my book
一定是刚才落下了
It must have fell out of my pocket.
我还以为你把坐标都记下来了
I thought you already figured out the coordinates.
我没有记下了 我把坐标记在书上
Well, I didn't memorize them I wrote them in the book
伙计们 我肯定他们还在四处找我们
I'm pretty sure they're still looking for us, guys.
算了 我们现在下水去
It's gone. now get in the damn water.
能不能帮下忙? 我儿子的照片
Would you please? it's a picture of my son.
你能不能
Can you, uh
放到包里去?
Put it in the bag?
见鬼去吧 马宏
Screw you, Mahone.
我们走
Let's go.
Mc格雷迪 Mc格雷迪?
McGrady. mcGrady?
我游泳很烂
I don't swim so good.
你说什么?
What?
太糟了 孩子 就是湿下水 来吧
Too bad, kid, you're getting wet. get in.
听着 没事的
Look it's all right.
我们共用氧气罐 抱紧我就行
We'll share tanks. just hold onto me
我们交替 10秒钟一次
And we'll switch off back and forth, ten seconds apiece.
走吧 我们走
Come on. let's go.
这里
over here
朝海滩那边
towards the beach
我很肯定
i could've sworn
他们是朝这个方向去的
they were headed in this direction
给我望远镜
give me the binoculars
看到船了么?
do you see any boats?
一条都没
not a one
他妈的 到底上哪去了?
where the hell are they?
斯科菲尔德哪去了?
Where is Scofield?
我不知道 他什么都没和我说
I don't know he didn't tell me nothing
他去了哪里?
Where is he running?
我告诉你了 我什么都不知道
I told you, I don't know nothing
是你逼我出重招的
Well, there's only one way to make certain of that.
派人手检查附近5公里
i want men covering five kilometers
东西两面 全部都要查
both east and west and check-points
沿海的公里也要查
on all coastal roads
经过的每辆车都要检查
every vehicle is to be searched
通知将军
contact the general
我需要立即加派人手
i need more men sent to me at once
我是梅塔斯狱长 我会增派人手过去
This is general Mestas. the men will be sent.
索胡 我希望每个犯人
And, Sojo, I expect every prisoner
今天都能押回索纳监狱
To be returned to Sona today.
分派第四分队过去
Dispatch fourth platoon.
听着 这太疯狂了
Hey, hey, look, man, this is getting crazy here.
我会认罪无视赦免证
Look, I'll plead guilty for ignoring the warrant.
我会出席法庭的听证会
I'll show up for the court hearings.
让我离开这里吧
Let me get out of here.
你看 这里到处是警报和枪械
You know, with this alarms and the guns,
让我很是心焦
They're making me a little nervous.
事情没了结之前 你哪里都不能去
Until things settle in, you go nowhere.
所以乖乖做好吧
So just sit tight.
第四分队去卡布里海滩支援
Urfo platoon goes to Cabrillo beach ahora.
那里
There
他在哪里?
Where is he?
你说谁呢?
Where's who?
苏克雷还有那艘船
Sucre with the boat.
抓紧了
Ju hold on.
你没事吧 都好吧?
You all right? you all right?
是的
Yeah.
我没事 我很好
I'm all right, I'm all right.
我们在这里呆着
We're not gonna make it
可不是长久之计啊 迈克
Out here too much longer, Michael.
苏克雷正在赶过来 耐心点
Sucre is coming. be patient.
不好意思
Excuse me?
312号船 怎么还在这里?
Boat 312, why is it still here?
今天不是应该有人开走的吗?
Wasn't someone supposed to take that out today?
确实有人定了 但是他们没有来取
Someone reserved it, but they never picked it up.
收到 长官
Yes, general.
汇报下最新进展
I want an update.
仍然没有任何线索 海滩上什么都没有
Still no sign of them. nothing on the coast.
我想他们可能又返回了丛林
I think they may have gone back into the jungle.
丛林? 是你让我派人去海滩的
The jungle? you asked me to send men to the beach
队长
Capitan
稍等下 长官
Just a moment, general.
长官 我们需要联系海岸警卫队
General, I think we have to call the coast guard.
抓好了
Come on
你没事吧?
You all right?
我的腿开始抽筋了
My legs are starting to cramp.
小兄弟 你得抓紧
You gotta hold on, buddy.
迈克 这样下去 坚持不了多久
We're not gonna last out here too long, Michael.
迈克 你的朋友呢?
Where's your friend, Michael?
苏克雷不会就这样把我们抛弃的
Sucre's not just gonna abandon us out here, all right?
他会来的 会来的
He'll show, he'll show.
海岸警卫队已经出动了4艘船了
The coast guard is launching four vessels
他们就这么一直泡在水里
They've been in the water this whole time.
或许现在都沉到海底去了
They're probably at the bottom of the ocean by now.
看看这个
Well, look it here
我们为酒鬼 行为反常的人开赦免令?
A drunk and disorderlyke we warrant for jorge rivera.han
无力支付孩子生活补助
Failure to pay child support.
什么样的人才会
What kind of man doesn't
不顾及自己家庭呢?
take care of his family?
不太好的人吧
Not a good one.
求你了 让我走吧
Please let me go
他们都在等我
they are waiting on me.
你哪也去不了
You're not going anywhere.
我们处理好你的问题 才能放你走
Once we're done processing you, then you can go.
乖乖做好 等吧
Until then, sit tight.
这个点 我该听到些动静了
I should have heard something by now.
我跟丢了所有的线索
I've lost all damn track of them.
布鲁斯想要回他儿子 总会来的
Burrows will eventually reach out if he wants his son ck.
没错 不过或许这样的筹码还不够
Yeah, well, that might no longer be an option.
看啊 快看
Look look
苏克雷
Sucre
他应该闪下灯的
He's supposed to be flashing a light.
林肯 他没有反应
He's not responding, Linc.
是海岸警卫队 他们发现我们了
The coast guard. they found us.
爸爸
Papa
迈克 迈克?
Michael Michael?
如果我没有生还的机会
If I don't get another chance, I want
我想你知道 我对你做的一切深表谢意
You to know that I appreciate everything you've done.
承谢了
You're welcome.
过来 儿子
Come on, son.
你怎么会找到我们的?
How'd you find us?
你后来再没现身 你说过你会来的
You never showed, and you said you'd be coming
从西南方来 所以我来碰碰运气
From the southwest, so I took a chance.
你认为苏克雷会发生什么事?
What do you think happened to Sucre?
我不知道 但是我们得赶紧走
Don't know, but we gotta move.
他不行了
He's done
那么他呢?
What about him?
他的情况更糟糕
He's even worse off.
还剩一个了
Guess that just leaves one.
起来
Get up.
我们走
Let's go.
我在后排看到盒子 所以就把车开来了
I saw the boxes in the back, so I took your car
猜想你需要换下装
Figured you'd need to change
脚踝伤怎样了?
How's the ankle?
真想把脚卸了
I need to get off my feet.
好了 伙计们 换下装束
All right, guys, get changed and make sure
确保没有落下任何湿衣服
You don't leave any wet clothes behind.
听着
Listen, uh
非常感谢
Thanks for everything.
谢谢你对我儿的关照
Thank you for my boy.
我希望你也尽快找回儿子
I hope you get your son back, too.
是的 我也是
Yeah, me, too.
我们回卡车去
Come. we need to get back to the truck.
迈克?
Michael?
谢谢你
Thank you.
路易 回到你的家庭去
Go be with your family, Luis.
喂
Yeah?
你们到底在哪呢?
Where the hell are you?
我们遇到些麻烦 正在赶去巴拿马
We ran into some trouble. we're-we're downtown panama.
不 林肯 你并没有去
No, Lincoln, you're not.
有人跟来了
We got company.
他们怎么能找到我们?
How'd they find us?
你跟上他们了?
You have them?
我们马上超上去了
We're right on top of them.
抓紧了
Hold on
他们或许盯上了格雷迪的老爸 对车动了手脚
They must've gotten to Grady's dad and bugged this car.
或者是我们中的一个
Or one of us.
那在水里的时候 他们怎么没有发现我们?
Then why didn't they find us when we were in the water?
那是因为水阻隔了信号
It's because the water was blocking the signal.
你还戴着格雷琴给你的手表干嘛呢?
What you do with that stopwatch that Gretchen gave you?
天啊 我不知道
Oh, my god. I didn't know.
我真不知道
I didn't know.
好了 抓紧了 伙计们
Okay, hold on, guys.
好了 这回该利用一下地形了
All right, it's time to use this rig to our advantage.
我们上路吧
Go here we go
这好像是条死路
Uh this is, like, a dead end right here.
别呆在车里
Stay in the car, then.
走这边
This way
为什么你就是不招呢
Why don't you just tell us what you know?
你不会想尝尝被打得半死的滋味吧
Then you won't wind up being beaten half to death
-就像你的朋友一样 -我不比你知道的多
Like your friend. I know less than you do.
孰轻孰重 你心知肚明
Which is hard, considering how dumb you are.
我想知道逃犯留下的所有蛛丝马迹
I want everything you can find on the men who escaped
我现在就想要
And I want it immediately.
他怎么还在这里?
What the hell is he still doing here?
除非是谋杀
Unless it's for murder
让他出去
get him out of here
去管办事员要你的东西
Go see the clerk about your stuff.
他们被包围了
They're barricaded.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
快回来
Get back
枪声一直没停
All that gunfire and they only
但他们只击中了你的车三次
Hit your car three times?
浑蛋
Son of a bi
听着 林肯 你干的漂亮
Listen, Linc, you've done a great job getting us
带我们脱离险境 但这没用
Out of the frying pan, but it'll be for nothing
如果我们最终被打死的话
If we end up back in the fire.
这儿没有交火 只是一个交易
There's no fire, just an exchange,
你就是交换品
Then I'm done with you.
你真认为就这么简单
You think it's that simple?
恩 他们要你 他们得到你 就这么简单
Yeah, they want you, they get you. it's that simple.
这和我无关 这关系到索菲亚和你儿子 迈克
This is not about me. it's about Sofia and ur son. Michael
告诉他 告诉他这些人
Tell him tell him these people
不会就这样让我们离开的
Won't just let us walk away.
我们在海滩上已经讨论了这件事 詹姆斯
We already had this discussion back at the beach, James,
你也被说服了
And you were outvoted.
你犯了个可怕的错误
You're making a terrible mistake.
有人会因此送命
People might die because of this.
脱掉裤子
Take off your pants.
你说什么 警官
Excuse me, ser?
我让你脱掉的裤子
I said take off your pants.
如果我知道你们这帮索纳的家伙会来这套
If I knew you boys partied in Sona like this,
我就不跑了
I never would have tried to escape.
一部手机
One cell phone.
一个钱包
One wallet.
还有些零钱
And some change.
还有些纸
There were some papers.
还有一份租船合同 我需要它
A boat-rental agreement. I need them.
我检查一下抽屉
I'll check the drawer.
脱掉裤子
Take them down.
拜托 老兄
Come on, now, hombre.
用不着阉了我吧
There's no need to refry my beans.
放聪明点
Always with the wise talk.
别说任何我们不想听得话
Never saying anything we want to hear.
现在 我只想听你的惨叫声
Now, all I want to hear are your screams.
不 不
No, no.
不 不 不 不 不 听着
No, no, no, no, no. listen.
我告诉过你 我什么也不知道
I told you, I don't know nothing.
不 事实上 我一无所知
No, actually, I don't know nothing.
我发誓 我发誓我什么都不知道
I swear. I swear I don't.
但他知道
But he does
他知道一切
He knows everything
别急着走 老兄
Hey not so fast, amigo.
帮把手
Hey. a little help.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
这是我们交易的地方
Where we're gonna make the exchange on our terms.
这后面有条密道 一有情况
There's a service road out back, just in case
-我们就闪 -对 如果你还有命闪的话
We want to get lost. yeah, assuming you're still alive.
你说什么
You still talking?
林肯
Linc?
是我
Yeah.
枪声的骗局干的不错
Gotta commend you on that boom box trick.
非常老道
Very sophisticated.
你只从家偷了这个么
You steal that one from home alone?
你中计了 婊子
You fell for it, bitch.
好吧 听着 如果想见到你儿子
All right, listen. if you wanna see your son
你别再带些枪手来了
You're not calling the shots anymore.
直到我得到lj
As long as I have lj .
直到我得到惠斯勒 你最好
As long as I got Whistler, u'yo gonna do exactly what
按照我说的做 你明白么
I say. you got it?
现在 听清楚
Now, listen up.
我们在一座废弃的仓库
We're at an abandoned
距离交换地点5英里远
Warehouse five miles down the road
20分钟后
From the barrios interchange. be there in 20 minutes
带我儿子来这儿
With my son.
那我到那之后呢
And once I get there?
那我们就这么等着
So now we wait.
对
Yeah.
这能行么
Think this'll work?
恩 没问题
Yeah, it'll work.
你 我和lj
You, me and lj.
好
Yeah.
我也希望mc格雷迪会没事
I just hope it works out for mcGrady, too.
不 不
Oh, no.
他们一定封锁了离开巴拿马的所有路
They must have closed all the roads out of panama.
爸爸 该怎么办?
Papa, what do we do?
掉头吧 爸爸
You gotta turn around, papa.
我不能被抓回索纳 不行的
I can't go back to sona. I can't.
我不管他说什么
I don't care what he says.
他是个罪犯 是个垃圾
He's a convict he's a piece of garbage.
我压根就不知道迈克·斯科菲尔德这个人
I don't know anything about this Michael Scofield guy.
将军
General.
这里是越狱犯的所有资料
Here is everything we have on the escaped prisoners.
你不认识迈克·斯科菲尔德 是吗?
You don't know Michael Scofield, is that right, jorge?
是的
Yes.
你确定不要再考虑一下是否认识他 费尔南多?
You sure you don't want to ange your story, Fernando?
这是什么?
What is this?
这会帮你缓解一下疼痛
This should help make you a decent brace.
谢谢
Thank you.
这里应该可以看到他们
Should be able to see them coming from up here.
你做的很好
You did great.
谢谢
Thanks.
我只是想要回LJ
I just want lj back, you know?
只是时间问题
It's just a matter of time.
是啊
Yeah.
考虑到在这鬼地方
Considering I don't have
没有小马做礼物 我只能说句再见了
A pony in this race
我想这是我们分道扬镳的地方
I guess this is where we say goodbay
你认为我我会就这么放你走?
Think I am going to let you just walk out of here?
你以为你能一走了之 在你对我们做了这些之后?
After what you did to us?
在你杀了我老爸之后?
What you did to my dad?
不能
No.
在海滩上我就想杀了你
I was gonna kill you at the beach,
但是我不想这样而使大家被抓
But I didn't want to do anything that was gonna get us caught.
你开枪杀了我父亲 但我会给你
You shot my dad in the back. I'm gonna give you
你没有给他的尊严
The courtesy you never gave him.
转过去
Turn around.
林肯 想想你都在干些什么?
Linc, think about what you are doing
林肯 你知道
You know, Linc
我被迫选择你的家人还是我的家人
I was told to choose between your family and mine.
这是我的选择
That was my option.
我选了我的家人
I chose mine.
去死吧
Go to hell.
林肯 你不需要这样做
Linc, you don't have to do this.
马宏
Mahone
我的卡车
Hey my truck
停下来
Stop
现在我们怎么办?
What are we gonna do now?